C++ ~ 90 reserve keywords
Java ~ 50
C ~ 32
python ~ 33

***
The more reserve keywords the more complex the lang is.
***


Preprocessor Directives: 
def: Starts with # and is a set of commands to the preprocessor.
The preprocessor does not understand c++ it only gets the source ready for the compiler.

Comments are removed prior to compile by the preprocessor.
Single Line comment: // This is a comment
Multi Line comment: /*

Still in comment
*/ 
out of comment.
*********************************************

Main function:
The main function is called upon the start of every c++ program, the int returned is the exit code.
main needs to return an integer!
Example of a program that takes in arguments.
int main (int argc, char *argv[]){
    //code
    return 0;
}

Scope resolution operator = ::
:: - Makes it possible to tell the compiler which scope is being referenced.
Namespaces: Containers to group functions and entities into a consolidated library.

Example of using a namespace:

using namespace std; // Use the entire namespace brings in all functions.
using std::cout; // Only brings in the specific function.

Basic IO using cin, cout, cerr, and clog.
endl: 
* Flushes stream
* Most applicable in file streams

cout:
* Standard output stream
* Output to Console

cin:
* Standard input stream
* Input from keyboard

<<:
* Insertion Operator
* Outputs to output streams

>>:
* Extraction Operator
* Outputs to input streams
